Do you want to know... What it is?
θελεις να μαθεις... τι ειναι;
The Matrix is everywhere.
το matrix ειναι παντου
It is all around us.
ειναι γυρω μας
Even now, in this very room.
ακομα και τωρα, σ'αυτό το δωματιο
You can see it when you look at your window,
μπορεις να το δεις οταν κοιτας το παραθυρο
or when you turn on your television.
η οταν ανοιγεις τη τηλεοραση
You can feel it when you go to the work,
μπορεις να το δεις οταν πας στη δουλεια
when you go to church,
οταν πας στην εκκλησια
when you pay your taxes.
οταν πληρωνεις τους φορους σου
It is the world that has been pulled over your eyes, to blind you from the truth.
Ειναι ο κοσμος που μπηκε μπροστα στα ματια σου για να σε τυφλωσει απο την αληθεια
What truth?
ποια αληθεια;
That you are a slave, Neo.
το οτι εισαι σκλαβος, Νιο
Like everyone else, you were born into bondage,
οπως ολοι, γεννηθηκες δεσμωτης
born into a prison that you can not smell or taste or touch.
γεννηθηκες σε μια φυλακη που δε μπορεις να μυρισεις, να γευτεις η να αγγιξεις
A prison...
μια φυλακη
for your mind.
για το μυαλο σου
Unfortunately, no one can be...
δυστυχως, κανεις δε μπορει
told what the Matrix is.
να μαθει τι ειναι το Ματριξ
You have to see it for yourself.
πρεπει να το δεις μονος σου
This is your last chance.
αυτη ειναι η τελευταια ευκαιρια σου
After this, there is no turning back.
μετα απ'αυτο, δεν υπαρχει επιστροφη
You take the blue pill...
αν παρεις το μπλε χαπι
The story ends...
η ιστορια τελειωνει
You wake up in your bed and believe whatever you want believe.
ξυπνας στο κρεβατι σου και πιστευεις οτι θες να πιστεψεις
You take the red pill,
αν παρεις το κοκκινο χαπι
you stay in Wonderland.
μενεις στη χωρα των θαυματων
And I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
και σου δειχνω ποσο βαθεια παει η κουνελοτρυπα
Remember...
θυμησου
All I am offering is the truth, nothing more.
το μονο που σου δινω ειναι η αληθεια, τιποτε αλλο
Follow me.
ακολουθησε με